<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tien Angel Nguyen</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tien Angel Nguyen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me!</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Background:I graduated from the University of Texas at Austin with a Bachelor of Science and Arts in Biology. I am a pre-med student with hopes of attending medical school in my near future. Aside from school work, I am quite involved with a local animal shelter in Austin, TX. I volunteer and foster for Austin Pets Alive! and it is so rewarding. I am a huge advocate for adopting animals and have two of my own!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Blog</title>
      <link>/blog/python-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/python-blog/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:In this blog, I will be writing about what I have learned in a Computational Biology course I took. Now if you were expecting a blog about snakes, I am sorry to disappoint; however, I promise this blog about the language Python is just as riveting! In this course, we were briefly introduced to Python. I will be including a few things that I found were interesting in this blog post such as using the package “Reticulate”, regular expression, and some things about python bioinformatics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World of Warcraft: Battlegrounds Analysis</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:In this project, I will be modeling, testing, and making predictions on a dataset created from observations on the game, World of Warcraft, which is a MMORPG created by Blizzard. This dataset contains information about battlegrounds, which are timed matches in an instanced area where players are able to compete against other players (PvP). Players are placed in teams on the basis of the faction that they belong to, the Alliance or the Horde, and their character’s level, so the matches consist of similar team compositions competing against one another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does Happiness Affect Life Expectancy?</title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction for this Data Analysis Project:In this project, I will be analyzing two datasets, lifeexpect and happiness2015. The dataset lifeexpect comes from the World Health Organization (WHO), and it contains information on global life expectancies. In addition, it contains a number of health variables contributing to the life expectancies. A few of these are GDP, diseases, schooling, and resources. The second dataset happiness2015 comes from The World Happiness Report, and it consists of information on global happiness in addition to variables contributing to this happiness value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects  Below are some projects that I have completed:   Does Happiness Affect Life Expectancy?
  World of Warcraft: Battlegrounds Analysis
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>